<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <rss version="2.0"><channel>
 <title>Gregory Anne</title>
	<description>Last Elements</description>
	<link>http://englishblazere.free.fr</link>
	<image>
	  <title>Gregory Anne</title>
	  <url>http://englishblazere.free.fr/images/ionetwork.jpg</url>
	  <link>http://englishblazere.free.fr</link>
	</image>
	<copyright>Gregory Anne</copyright>
	<webMaster>englishblazere@free.fr</webMaster>
 
 
 
 <item><title>Last Experience</title><link>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#experience</link><guid>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#experience</guid><pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2009 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<table align="center" border="2" summary="your browser cannot display tables"><tbody>
<tr>
<th>Organization</th>
<th>Date</th>
<th>Role / Nature of work</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
			
		<a href="http://www.ionetwork.com"> 
		<img src="../images/ionetwork.jpg" alt="IO-Network" width="120" height="70" border="0" />
		</a> <br/>Ho Chi Minh City (Vietnam)
	
		
			</td>
<td>
		October 2009 till now
			</td>
<td>
		Project Manager 
		<br/> <big>Manages a 6-person team</big>
		<br/> <big>Project Management, R&amp;D &amp; Solutioning</big>
		<br/> <big>Needs analysis alongside with customers</big>, Specification &amp; Design 
		<br/> Technologies: Transaction Host: Java, Microsoft SQL Server, Eclipse <br/> 
		Terminal programming: Verifone Vx510, ARM Compiler, Source Insight, C <br/> 
		Miscellaneous: UML, SVN, Testlink, Mantis, Google Apps...
		<br/> Payment Solutions projects for South-East Asian market:
		<ol> 
		<li> Pre-paid Top-up Systems for mobile phone suppliers (I achieved several upgrades
		on the main customer's running system) </li> 
		<li> Gift Cards, Loyalty Cards and management systems (I promoted and sold the system
		customers, also enhanced functionalities)</li> 
		<li> Electronic Cash Registers: I created a middleware software to interact between
		the terminal connected via RS232 and any retail management application. I specified 
		the packets sent via serial between the ECR and the terminal, adapted for Softpay. I implemented
		the exhange of these messages in Java using Javacomm API. Finally I provided a
		standardized access to this middleware application using <big>CORBA</big>. Then I coached 
		the team in the partner company (<a href="http://www.evietsoft.net/GCMS.aspx">evietsoft</a>), 
		helped them to create the CORBA client able to use our middleware application. </li>
<li> iPay: an online payment functionality for Gift Cards System (which I entirely designed)</li> 
		<li> VIP Service: I created an add-on to iPay to identify members using QR codes and
process vip rewards. The QR code scanner uses <a href="http://replycam.com/">replycam.com</a>: a flash client for
webcams.
 
		</li><li> Bill Collectors: I specified an add-on for Gift cards system and iPay, so card
holders have the possibility to pay their bills using our prepaid accounts.
 </li>
		<li> Lines Encryption System between Point-Of-Sales and banking application servers
		(I introduced the product at the banks headquarters, I installed a pilot version for the biggest state-owned bank in the country)</li>		
		<li> NFC Payment System &amp; devices (using Proximity Coupling Device - 
		I specified the flow of transactions and all other main aspects for several projects
		bound to this technology)</li>	
		<li> Funds Transfer (I partnered a US Corporation to organize Prepaid and
			Mastercard-based funds transfers between North America and Vietnam using SMS)</li>
		<li> Integration of various applications on a standalone terminal </li>
		</ol>
		As a department lead, I also worked at improving the process (I defined the strategy
		guidelines, I created workflows for maintenance and new developments and I also 
		brought a quality approach).
			</td>
</tr>
</tbody></table>]]></description></item><item><title>Last Degree</title><link>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#education</link><guid>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#education</guid><pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2009 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<table align="center" border="2" summary="your browser cannot display tables"><tbody><tr><th>Year</th><th>Degree</th><th>Summary</th></tr><tr><td>2009
		</td><td>
		<big>MASTER</big>2 PRO Information and Systems Science (<big>MSc</big>)<br/> 
	speciality Computer Science major <a href="http://www.lsis.org/master/index.php?parcours=3"> Software Engineering </a> <br/>
	Honors: <big>magna cum laude - 2:1</big> - (<a href="http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mention_honorifique">mention bien</a>)<br/> 
	Universite Aix-Marseille III <br/>
		(5th year of university)
		</td><td>
		As  is common in France, I had chosen to study the second year of my major at a different institute, 
		as courses are compatible between different universities. 
		I studied Software Engineering major in my 2nd year of masters the purpose of which 
		is to prepare students for the job market. The courses provided us the access to any
		part of an SDLC (we were trained to manage projects, specify, design, implement, and control the quality).
		</td></tr></tbody></table>]]></description></item></channel></rss>