<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <rss version="2.0"><channel>
 <title>Gregory Anne</title>
	<description>Last Elements</description>
	<link>http://englishblazere.free.fr</link>
	<image>
	  <title>Gregory Anne</title>
	  <url>http://englishblazere.free.fr/images/ionetwork.jpg</url>
	  <link>http://englishblazere.free.fr</link>
	</image>
	<copyright>Gregory Anne</copyright>
	<webMaster>englishblazere@free.fr</webMaster>
 
 
 
 <item><title>Last Experience</title><link>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#experience</link><guid>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#experience</guid><pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2009 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<table align="center" border="2" summary="your browser cannot display tables"><tbody>
<tr>
<th>Organization</th>
<th>Date</th>
<th>Role / Nature of work</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
			<a href="http://www.apteagroup.fr"> 
				<img src="http://englishblazere.free.fr/img/aptea.jpg" alt="Aptea" width="120" height="70" border="0" />
			</a> <br/>Boulogne-Billancourt (Paris Region)
		
		</td>
<td>
		Since January 2012
		
		</td>
<td>
			<big><b>Jr Project Management Officer</b></big>
			<br/><br/>Since I arrived immediately after the deal was concluded, I had the honour and pleasure to initiate the 
			development of the project (1000 MD) basing on the scope statements and the RFP answer.
			<br/><br/>I co-wrote a QA & QC project plans document, basing on a V-model. The project purpose is refactoring 
			a whole information system, integrating it along with a web portal, and adding new workflow rules (domain: public service)
			<br/><br/>A long business analysis phase supported by the client allowed me to write the detailed SRS document, which I splitted
			out in several volumes, concerning each main skill component of the project. This document uses basically UML and BPM standards.
			<br/><br/>I studied the technologies that could be embedded in the architecture and documented 
			them for the team which would be joining me soon.
			<br/><br/>I led the build of a prototype with SpringMVC - EJB3 - JPA - Solr - BonitaSoft - and JQuery UI mock-ups. 
			Created a development environment with Eclipse-Maven-SVN.
			<br/><br/>I am today in charge of all business concerns for the team, which members are now making the software.
		</td>
</tr>
</tbody></table>]]></description></item><item><title>Last Degree</title><link>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#education</link><guid>http://englishblazere.free.fr/en/index.php?p=mycv#education</guid><pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2009 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<table align="center" border="2" summary="your browser cannot display tables"><tbody><tr><th>Year</th><th>Degree</th><th>Summary</th></tr><tr><td>2009
		</td><td>
		<big>MASTER</big>2 PRO Information and Systems Science (<big>MSc</big>)<br/> 
	speciality Computer Science major <a href="http://www.lsis.org/master/index.php?parcours=3"> Software Engineering </a> <br/>
	Honors: <big>magna cum laude - 2:1</big> - (<a href="http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mention_honorifique">mention bien</a>)<br/> 
	Universite Aix-Marseille III <br/>
		(5th year of university)
		</td><td>
		As  is common in France, I had chosen to study the second year of my major at a different institute, 
		as courses are compatible between different universities. 
		I studied Software Engineering major in my 2nd year of masters the purpose of which 
		is to prepare students for the job market. The courses provided us the access to any
		part of an SDLC (we were trained to manage projects, specify, design, implement, and control the quality).
		</td></tr></tbody></table>]]></description></item></channel></rss>