
<education>
	<item>
		<year>2009
		</year>
		<degree>
		<big>MASTER</big>2 PRO Information and Systems Science (<big>MSc</big>)<br/> 
	speciality Computer Science major <a href="http://www.lsis.org/master/index.php?parcours=3"> Software Engineering </a> <br/>
	Honors: <big>magna cum laude - 2:1</big> - (<a href="http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mention_honorifique">mention bien</a>)<br/> 
	Universite Aix-Marseille III <br/>
		(5th year of university)
		</degree>
		<text>
		As  is common in France, I had chosen to study the second year of my major at a different institute, 
		as courses are compatible between different universities. 
		I studied Software Engineering major in my 2nd year of masters the purpose of which 
		is to prepare students for the job market. The courses provided us the access to any
		part of an SDLC (we were trained to manage projects, specify, design, implement, and control the quality).
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<year>
		2008
		</year>
		<degree>
		<a href="http://yaubry.univ-tln.fr/Descriptif.UE.html"> MASTER1- Information and Systems Science  </a>
	<br/> (MSc) with Honors cum laude - 2:2
	<br/> Universite de Toulon et du Var (South of France) 
	<br/>(4th year of university)
		</degree>
		<text>
		Each year my courses became more and more oriented in the domain I chose 
and from this year onwards I have only been studying really modern techologies. We had projects to
analyse in a case study and then to develop.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<year>2007
		</year>
		<degree>
		GRADUATION Science and Technologies (BSc) <br/>speciality Computer Science major Computer Science.
	<br/> Universite de Toulon et du Var  
	<br/>(3rd year of university)
		</degree>
		<text>
		I got reoriented from a Mathematics Degree and so,
	 to be able to carry out computer science projects I had to learn a lot by myself,
	 mostly about the web and the operating systems. Meanwhile, when I had a course on object oriented programming concepts,
	 I could learn the use of graphical libraries and added a very personal touch to a project.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<year>2005
		</year>
		<degree>
		UNDERGRADUATE DEGREE Mathematics and Computer Science Engineering
	<br/>  (major Applied Mathematics for Industry)
	<br/> 	Universite Joseph Fourier	Grenoble (French Alps)  
	<br/>(2nd year of university)
		</degree>
		<text>
		I was  part of an Engineering School whose  major is to develop Mathematics Research 
	using Computer Science Tools. So we  learnt both Mathematics (with algebra, analysis, optimization, probabilities)
	 and Computer Science.
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<year>2004
		</year>
		<degree>
		passed first year of university in Science and Technologies
		</degree>
	</item>
	<item>
		<year>2002
		</year>
		<degree>
		General Baccalaureate major Science with Honors cum laude - 2:2<br/>La Seyne/mer(83)
		</degree>
	</item>
</education>

