
<experience>
	<item>
			<organization>
			
		<a href="http://www.ionetwork.com"> 
		<img src="../images/ionetwork.jpg" alt="IO-Network" width="120" height="70" border="0" />
		</a> <br/>Ho Chi Minh City (Vietnam)
	
		
			</organization>
			<date>
		October 2009 till now
			</date>
			<role>
		Project Manager 
		<br/> <big>Manages a 6-person team</big>
		<br/> <big>Project Management, R&amp;D &amp; Solutioning in networks and cryptography</big>
		<br/> <big>Needs analysis alongside with customers</big>, Specification &amp; Design 
		<br/> Technologies: Java, C, Microsoft SQL Server, UML, CVS, Eclipse, Testlink, DotProject.
		<br/> Payment Solutions projects for South-East Asian market:
		<ol> 
		<li> Pre-paid Top-up Systems for mobile phone suppliers (I achieved several upgrades
		on the main customer's running system) </li> 
		<li> Gift Cards, Loyalty Cards and management systems </li> 
		<li> iPay: an online payment functionality for Gift Cards System (which I entirely designed)</li> 
		<li> Embedded application for credit cards payment, integration with Electronic Cash Register 
		(I specified the requirements to ECR developers)</li>	
		<li> Lines Encryption System between Point-Of-Sales and banking application servers
		(I introduced the product at the banks headquarters)</li>		
		<li> Touch'n'Go Payment System &amp; devices (using Proximity Coupling Device - 
		I specified the flow of transactions and all other main aspects for several projects
		bound to this technology)</li>
		<li> Integration of various applications on a standalone terminal </li>
		</ol>
		As a department lead, I also worked at improving the process (I defined the strategy
		guidelines, I created workflows for maintenance and new developments and I also 
		brought a quality approach).
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			 <a href="http://www.ibm.com/vn/en/"> 
		<img src="../images/ibm.jpg" alt="IBM" width="140" height="60" border="0" /><br/>
		<big>Vietnam Global Delivery Center</big></a> <br/>Ho Chi Minh City (Vietnam)
			</organization>
			<date>
			March to August 2009
			</date>
			<role>
			<u>Officially agreed end of studies internship :</u> 
		<br/> Contributed to "MdP" team projects, expert in Java/J2E technologies
		 (collaborative working based on <big>Hibernate/Spring/Struts frameworks, Mantis bugtracker, Subversion</big>)
		<br/>Status and tasks evoluted regarding projects:		 
		 <ol>
		<li>Knowledge Base Portal:<br/>
I supplied solutions (CMS comparisons).<br/>
&amp; Installed &amp; Customized &amp; Administrated the CMS EZ-Publish<br/>
&amp; Promoted the use of the portal to the team.</li>
<li>
I developed complete screens of web applications based on Java framework
Hibernate / Spring / Struts (Using HQL, JSP, JavaScript, XML, CSS and JEE
concepts)<br/>
I corrected bugs and executed change-requests on this JEE web application.
</li>
<li>
Business analyst: I was a relay between IBM VN and IBM FR<br/>
I translated documents from French to English, I detailed the specifications, and I
filtered out the possible ambiguities.
</li>
<li>
Internal project:<br/>
I had the honour to manage a 1-to-4-persons team depending on the iteration (spiral lifecycle). The
project was managed following MdP workflow (estimations,
planning and tracking). For each iteration I investigated to answer the needs,
searching and proposing my solutions. I contributed greatly in the specification
and design of the model, I helped my team in their LAMP or WAMP server or IDE
configuration, and I also contributed in implementing the most complex parts
(using MySQL, PHP, JavaScript/AJAX)
</li>
<li>
I supplied my ideas about the model design and also technical elements into the
context of a new offer
</li>
<li>
IBM Formations:<br/>
Function Points: methods to estimate the charge of projects<br/>
Quality Process Awareness and Competency Evaluation: Understanding the concepts of quality assurance<br/>
CMMI Awareness: Participation in training sessions with
a view to the certification of the development center
</li>
		 
		</ol>
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			 <a href="http://www.osiatis.fr/"> 
		<img src="../images/Logo_Osiatis.jpg" alt="Osiatis" width="140" height="60" border="0" /><br/>
		</a> IT Outsourcing Services <br/>Vitrolles -near Marseille-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2008
			</date>
			<role>
			Administrated the professionnal database management system "Remedy" for EUROCOPTER at Marignane <br/>
		+ Created a videoconferencing rooms directory (SQL, PHP)
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Senecrus Co <br/> Rungis -near Paris-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2007
			</date>
			<role>
			Chief machine operator, managed staff and upkept the material in a shrimps transformation and conditioning factory
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Mathematics lessons<br/>Lorgues/La Valette <br/> -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			June 2007
			</date>
			<role>
			Private tutoring for high school students with various levels
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			CMC-Animations<br/>Toulon -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Christmas 2006
			</date>
			<role>
			Giant fluffy in the great Christmas parades.
			Dancing and snapshots with the kids.
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			<a href="http://www.mobilegov.com">
		<img src="../images/mobilegov.jpg" alt="Mobilegov" width="160" height="50" border="0" /><br/>
		</a>Sophia-Antipolis -French Riviera-
			</organization>
			<date>
			2006
			</date>
			<role>
			 <u> Officially agreed internship 2006 : </u> 
		Testing, Quality Control for java applications, writing technical documentations and user guides.
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Hypermarket E. Leclerc<br/>Le Luc -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2005
			</date>
			<role>
			Versatile employee in liquids shelves
		Using hand and power pallet trucks
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Atelier V<br/>
			Carros -near Nice-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2004
			</date>
			<role>
			Manufacturing roadsigns for the works
		of Nice's streetcar
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Total Service Station<br/>
			Le Cannet -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Fall 2003
			</date>
			<role>
			In charge of sales and restocking shelves, using cash
		register, serving petrol, opening and closing of the station
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Town Hall<br/>
			Le Luc
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2003
			</date>
			<role>
			Arranging festivities,
		general maintenance of the spaces
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Chateau la Lauzade<br/>
			Le Luc
			</organization>
			<date>
			September 2002
			</date>
			<role>
			Grape harvest
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Qualimedia Plus<br/>
			Nice
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2000
			</date>
			<role>
			Computers shop in removal :
        	various work, setting up material
			</role>
	</item>
</experience>