
<experience>
	<item>
		<organization>
			<a href="http://www.aptea.net"> 
				<img src="http://englishblazere.free.fr/img/aptea.jpg" alt="Aptea" width="120" height="70" border="0" />
			</a> <br/>Boulogne-Billancourt (Paris Region)
		
		</organization>
		<date>
		Since January 2012
		
		</date>
		<role>
			<big><b><u>Jr Project Management Officer</u></b></big>
			<br/><br/>BA leader (2 years) + technical leader (2nd year). 
<br/><br/>
Aptea is a French IT Outsourcing company specializing in software for business that is particularly sensitive and complex (Energy and Transport).
<br/><br/>
Since I joined Aptea, I have been assigned to one customer only (public official establishment) and I carried out a 2000md project.
<br/><br/>
V-Lifecycle: I co-guided the business analysis and wrote the SRS. <br/>
I designed the architecture and integrated the first components. <br/>
I developed whole parts of the software, including the totality of the model layer of the software and the migration scripts. <br/>
I managed partly the customer interface and integrated change requests. <br/>
I tested and validated the software. <br/>
<br/>
Environment: SQL Server, Oracle DB, Glassfish, JAVA/JEE (JPA2, Hibernate, EJB3, Spring3 MVC, Maven), JQuery, Bootstrap Twitter, Lucene, 
		XSL, Digital Signature, WebDav(Milton), NetBeans, SVN, Mantis, Jenkins, DokuWiki, 
		Testlink, UML, BPML, French.
		</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			
		<a href="http://www.ionetwork.com"> 
		<img src="../img/ionetwork.jpg" alt="IO-Network" width="120" height="70" border="0" />
		</a> <br/>Ho Chi Minh City (Vietnam)
	
		
			</organization>
			<date>
		October 2009 to October 2011
			</date>
			<role>
		<big><b><u>Project Manager </u></b></big>
		<br/><br/> <big>Manages a 6-person team</big>
		<br/> <big>Project Management, R&amp;D &amp; Solutioning</big>
		<br/> <big>Needs analysis alongside with customers</big>, Specification &amp; Design 
		<br/> Technologies: Transaction Host: Java, Microsoft SQL Server, Eclipse <br/> 
		Terminal programming: Verifone Vx510, ARM Compiler, Source Insight, C <br/> 
		Miscellaneous: UML, SVN, Testlink, Mantis, Google Apps...
		<br/> Payment Solutions projects for South-East Asian market:
		<ol> 
		<li> Pre-paid Top-up Systems for mobile phone suppliers: I achieved several upgrades
		on the main customer's running system. </li> 
		<li> Gift Cards, Loyalty Cards and management systems: I promoted and sold the system
		to prospects, also enhanced functionalities</li> 
		<li> Electronic Cash Registers: I created a middleware software to interact between
		the terminal connected via RS232 and any retail management application. I specified 
		the packets sent via serial between the ECR and the terminal, adapted for Softpay. I implemented
		the exhange of these messages in Java using Javacomm API. Finally I provided a
		standardized access to this middleware application using <big>CORBA</big>. Then I coached 
		the team in the partner company (<a href="http://www.evietsoft.net/GCMS.aspx">evietsoft</a>), 
		helped them to create the CORBA client able to use our middleware application. </li>
<li> iPay: an online payment functionality for Gift Cards System (which I entirely designed)</li> 
		<li> VIP Service: I created an add-on to iPay to identify members using QR codes and
process vip rewards. The QR code scanner uses <a href="http://replycam.com/">replycam.com</a>: a flash client for
webcams.
 
		</li>
	<li> PrepaidWebServices: I created a JAX-WS application to let customer accounts download transactions and cards
	reports in XML format.
 
		</li><li> Bill Collectors: I specified an add-on for Gift cards system and iPay, the aim of
		which is to provide the card holders the possibility to pay their bills using our prepaid accounts.
 </li>
		<li> Lines Encryption System between Point-Of-Sales and banking application servers: 
		I introduced the product at the banks headquarters, I installed a pilot version for the biggest state-owned bank in the country)</li>		
		<li> NFC Payment System &amp; devices: using Proximity Coupling Device, 
		I specified the use cases (flows of transactions) for several projects bound to this technology</li>	
		<li> Funds Transfer: I partnered a US Corporation to organize Prepaid and
			Mastercard-based funds transfers between North America and Vietnam using SMS</li>
		<li> Integration of various applications on a standalone terminal </li>
		</ol>
		As a department lead, I also worked at improving the process (I defined the strategy
		guidelines, I created workflows for maintenance and new developments and I also 
		brought a quality approach).
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			 <a href="http://www.ibm.com/vn/en/"> 
		<img src="../img/ibm.jpg" alt="IBM" width="140" height="60" border="0" /><br/>
		<big>Vietnam Global Delivery Center</big></a> <br/>Ho Chi Minh City (Vietnam)
			</organization>
			<date>
			March to August 2009
			</date>
			<role>
			<u>Officially agreed end of studies internship :</u> 
		<br/> Contributed to "MdP" team projects, expert in Java/J2E technologies
		 (collaborative working based on <big>Hibernate/Spring/Struts frameworks, Mantis bugtracker, Subversion</big>)
		<br/>Status and tasks evolved regarding projects:		 
		 <ol>
		<li>Knowledge Base Portal:<br/>
I supplied solutions (CMS comparisons).<br/>
&amp; Installed &amp; Customized &amp; Administrated the CMS EZ-Publish<br/>
&amp; Promoted the use of the portal to the team.</li>
<li>
I developed complete screens of web applications based on Java framework
 (Using HQL, JSP, JavaScript, XML, CSS and JEE concepts)<br/>
I corrected bugs and executed change-requests on this JEE web application.
</li>
<li>
Business analyst: I was a relay between IBM VN and IBM FR<br/>
I translated documents from French to English, I detailed the specifications, and I
filtered out the possible ambiguities.
</li>
<li>
Internal project:<br/>
I had the honour to manage a 1-to-4-person team depending on the iteration (spiral lifecycle). The
project was managed following MdP workflow (estimations,
planning and tracking). For each iteration I investigated into the needs,
searched and proposed my solutions. I contributed greatly in the specification
and design of the model, I helped my team in their LAMP or WAMP server or IDE
configuration, and I also implemented the most complex parts
(using MySQL, PHP, JavaScript/AJAX)
</li>
<li>
I supplied my ideas about the model design and also technical elements into the
context of a new offer
</li>
<li>
IBM Formations:<br/>
Function Points: methods to estimate the charge of projects<br/>
Quality Process Awareness and Competency Evaluation: Understanding the concepts of quality assurance<br/>
CMMI Awareness: Participation in training sessions with
a view to the certification of the development center
</li>
		 
		</ol>
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			 <a href="http://www.osiatis.fr/"> 
		<img src="../img/Logo_Osiatis.jpg" alt="Osiatis" width="140" height="60" border="0" /><br/>
		</a> IT Outsourcing Services <br/>Vitrolles -near Marseille-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2008
			</date>
			<role>
			Administrated the professionnal database management system "Remedy" for EUROCOPTER at Marignane <br/>
		+ Created a videoconferencing rooms directory (SQL, PHP)
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Senecrus Co <br/> Rungis -near Paris-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2007
			</date>
			<role>
			Chief machine operator, managed staff and upkept the material in a shrimps transformation and conditioning factory
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Mathematics lessons<br/>Lorgues/La Valette <br/> -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			June 2007
			</date>
			<role>
			Private tutoring for high school students with various levels
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			CMC-Animations<br/>Toulon -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Christmas 2006
			</date>
			<role>
			Giant fluffy in the great Christmas parades.
			Dancing and snapshots with the kids.
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			<a href="http://www.mobilegov.com">
		<img src="../img/mobilegov.jpg" alt="Mobilegov" width="160" height="50" border="0" /><br/>
		</a>Sophia-Antipolis -French Riviera-
			</organization>
			<date>
			2006
			</date>
			<role>
			 <u> Officially agreed internship 2006 : </u> 
		Quality Control for java applications, wrote technical documentations and user guides.
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Hypermarket E. Leclerc<br/>Le Luc -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2005
			</date>
			<role>
			Versatile employee in liquids shelves
		Using hand and power pallet trucks
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Atelier V<br/>
			Carros -near Nice-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2004
			</date>
			<role>
			Manufacturing roadsigns for the works
		of Nice's streetcar
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Total Service Station<br/>
			Le Cannet -south of France-
			</organization>
			<date>
			Fall 2003
			</date>
			<role>
			In charge of sales and restocking shelves, using cash
		register, serving petrol, opening and closing of the station
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Town Hall<br/>
			Le Luc
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2003
			</date>
			<role>
			Arranging festivities,
		general maintenance of the spaces
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Chateau la Lauzade<br/>
			Le Luc
			</organization>
			<date>
			September 2002
			</date>
			<role>
			Grape harvest
			</role>
	</item>
	<item>
			<organization>
			Qualimedia Plus<br/>
			Nice
			</organization>
			<date>
			Summer 2000
			</date>
			<role>
			Computers shop in removal :
        	various work, setting up material
			</role>
	</item>
</experience>
