<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<glossary>
	<item>
		<term>IO Network</term>
		<definition>Joint Stock Company established in two services: Payment Solutions and Digital Marketing
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.ionetwork.com">http://www.ionetwork.com</a>
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>72</like>
		<master>95</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>R&amp;D</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> 
	Research and Development is the creative work undertaken on a systematic basis 
	in order to increase the stock of knowledge, and the use of this stock to devise new
	applications.
<br/><br/>
<u>@IO-Network:</u> 
The company wants to increase its potential in order to be independant from Singapour's partners
who usually supply the solutions.
<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>92</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Solutioning</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> 
	Software and hardware solutions research organized at special offers from clients.
<br/>
<br/>
<u>@IO-Network:</u> Design of proposals to clients, these proposals must meet
the exact client needs and available (directly or from partners) technologies.
<br/><br/></definition>
<like>70</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CVS</term>
		<definition> Control Version System 
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.nongnu.org/cvs/">http://www.nongnu.org/cvs/</a></definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Java</term>
		<definition> <u>Definition:</u> Technology developed by Sun Microsystems, 
	object-oriented language, inspired from C and C++, compiled code is run on a 
	Java Virtual Machine (highly portable) 
	<br/></definition>
		<like>85</like>
		<master>85</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>C / C++</term>
		<definition> <u>Definition:</u> C is a general-purpose computer programming language developed in 1972.
	C was designed for implementing system software.
	C++ is the object-oriented programming version of C.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>55</like>
		<master>75</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>UML</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> Unified Modeling Language<br/>
	A set of graphical notation techniques to create visual models of software-intensive systems.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>90</like>
		<master>95</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Testlink</term>
		<definition>TestLink enables easily to create and manage Test cases as well as organize
	 them into Test plans. These Test plans allow team members to execute Test cases and 
	 track test results dynamically, generate reports, trace software requirements, 
	 prioritize and assign tasks.
	 <br/><br/>
	 <u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.teamst.org/">http://www.teamst.org/</a>
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>85</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>DotProject</term>
		<definition>Project Management application. It is an open-source software and free for any uses 
	and is maintained by an open community of volunteer programmers.
	 <br/><br/>
	 <u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.dotproject.net/">http://www.dotproject.net/</a>
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>35</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Prepaid Top-up System</term>
		<definition>In South-East Asia, mobile phone suppliers don't work with substriction but credits.
	Various topup systems are proposed to the end-users so that they can top-up their credits.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<master>95</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Touch'n'Go</term>
		<definition>A Payment system being a substitue to cash. For small amounts a magnetic card can be used
	without any PIN input. This system is widely used in Malaysia and Israel. This project is
	mostly oriented in research.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>70</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>IBM</term>
		<definition>International Business Machines
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u><a href="http://www.ibm.com/vn/en/">http://www.ibm.com/vn/en/</a>
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>20</like>
		<master>95</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JEE</term>
		<definition>Java Entreprise Edition</definition>
		<like>83</like>
		<master>66</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Hibernate/Spring/Struts</term>
		<definition>Framework for rapid web applications development
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Hibernate:</u> Adaption of relational databases to the object paradigm.
	DB access is subsituted by method calls of high-level objects.
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Spring:</u> Multi-layer framework being used on all MVC approaches. Thus it can enable the
	integration of Hibernate for the persistance layer or Struts for the presentation
	layer.
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Struts:</u> Framework enabling the easy design of forms in web applications using
	actions. Struts also enables the automation of some features such as the data validation
	on users inputs of the interface.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>75</like>
		<master>60</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Framework</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> A software framework is a re-usable design for a software system
		</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Subversion</term>
		<definition>(SVN) is a version control system. It is used to maintain current and historical
	 versions of files such as source code, web pages, and documentation. Its goal is to be 
	 a mostly-compatible successor to the widely used CVS
	 <br/> <br/> 
	 <u>Website:</u><a href="http://subversion.tigris.org/">http://subversion.tigris.org/</a></definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Mantis</term>
		<definition>Bugtracking system, it allow users to record document and keep track of issues during
	a software development
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u><a href="http://www.mantisbt.org/">http://www.mantisbt.org/</a>
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>78</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CMS</term>
		<definition>Content Management System
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.cmsmatrix.org/">http://www.cmsmatrix.org/</a></definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>HQL</term>
		<definition>Hibernate Query Language</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JSP</term>
		<definition>Java Server Pages creates dynamically generated web pages, with HTML, XML, or other
	 document types
	 <br/><br/></definition>
		<like>70</like>
		<master>82</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JavaScript</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> Language primarily for client-side programming, implemented as an integrated 
	component of the web browser, allowing the development of enhanced user interfaces 
	and dynamic websites.
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>98</like>
		<master>85</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>XML</term>
		<definition>eXtensible Markup Language is a set of rules for encoding documents electronically.
	It is an easy to share and transmit way to organize databases, it becomes a standard for
	indexing information on the internet: what we call semantic web
	<br/><br/></definition>
		<like>98</like>
		<master>92</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CSS</term>
		<definition>Cascading Style Sheets</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>VN</term>
		<definition>Vietnam</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>FR</term>
		<definition>France</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Change Request</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u>Request for an adjustment or an evolution on a system expressed by the client.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Business Analysis</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u>Discipline of identifying business needs and determining solutions to business problems.
	 Solutions often include a systems development component</definition>
	 <like>72</like>
	 <master>88</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Lifecycle</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u>Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) in systems engineering and software engineering, 
	is the process of creating or altering systems, and the models and methodologies that 
	people use to develop these systems.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Workflow</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> A workflow consists of a sequence of connected steps. 
	It is a depiction of a sequence of operations, declared as work of a person, 
	a group of persons, an organization of staff, or one or more simple or complex mechanisms.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Tracking</term>
		<definition><u>Definition:</u> Determination process of the current and past state (and spare information) of an item
	(production object or resource) </definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>LAMP / WAMP</term>
		<definition>Linux Apache MySQL PHP / Windows AMP
	<br/><br/>
	<u>Website:</u> <a href="http://www.apachefriends.org/en/xampp.html">http://www.apachefriends.org/en/xampp.html</a></definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>IDE</term>
		<definition>Integrated Development Environment</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>MySQL / Postgres / Oracle</term>
		<definition>DBMS Exemples</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>PHP</term>
		<definition>Hypertext Preprocessor is a widely used, general-purpose scripting language that 
	was originally designed for web development, to produce dynamic web pages. It can be 
	embedded into HTML and generally runs on a web server, which needs to be configured to
	 process PHP code and create web page content from it.</definition>
	 <like>96</like>
	 <master>90</master>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>AJAX</term>
		<definition>Asynchronous JavaScript And XML</definition>
		<like>97</like>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Function Points</term>
		<definition>Charge estimation of projects by the number of features to be developed</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CMMI</term>
		<definition>Capability Maturity Model + Integration</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>IT</term>
		<definition>Information Technology</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Remedy</term>
		<definition>IT parks management system</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Eurocopter</term>
		<definition>EADS helicopters manufacturing branch</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>SQL</term>
		<definition>Structured Query Language</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>BSc</term>
		<definition>Bachelor degree of Science</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>MSc</term>
		<definition>Masters degree of Science</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>BPM</term>
		<definition>Business Process Modeling</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>HMI</term>
		<definition>Human-Machine Interface</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>ISO9001</term>
		<definition>International Organization for Standardization</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>SADT / SART</term>
		<definition>Specific Analysis and Design Techniques / Specific Analysis in Real-Time</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CASE Tools</term>
		<definition>Computer-Aided Software Engineering</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Automatons</term>
		<definition>Tools to describe the behavior of a system</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Petri nets</term>
		<definition>One of several mathematical modeling languages for the description of discrete distributed systems.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>NetBeans</term>
		<definition>A platform for the development of applications for the network 
	(using Java, JavaScript, PHP, Python, Ruby, Groovy, C, and C++), 
	and an integrated development environment (IDE) developed using the NetBeans Platform.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Eclipse</term>
		<definition>Multi-language software development environment comprising an IDE and a plug-in system 
	to extend it. It is written primarily in Java and can be used to develop applications in 
	Java and, by means of the various plug-ins, in other languages as well, including C, C++, 
	COBOL, Python, Perl, PHP, and others.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JDBC</term>
		<definition>Java Database Connector</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Log4J</term>
		<definition>A Java-based logging utility.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>License4J</term>
		<definition>A Java library for creating and validating licenses.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JTidy</term>
		<definition>HTML Tidy is an open source program and library for checking and generating clean XHTML/HTML.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JUnit</term>
		<definition>A unit testing framework for the Java programming language.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>RMI</term>
		<definition>Remote Method Invocation</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JMS</term>
		<definition>Java Message Service</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>EJB</term>
		<definition>Entity Java Bean</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>JBoss</term>
		<definition>A free software/open-source Java EE-based application server.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Procedural Languages</term>
		<definition>PL/SQL (Procedural Language/Structured Query Language) is Oracle Corporation's
	 procedural extension language for SQL. MySQL and Postgres also offer Procedural 
	 Languages developed on this model.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>DDL, DML, DCL, DQL</term>
		<definition>Database Definition Language, Database Manipulation Language, Database Control
	Language, Database Query Language</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>DBMS</term>
		<definition>Database Management System</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>XHTML</term>
		<definition>Extensible Hypertext Markup Language, or XHTML, is a family of XML markup 
	languages that mirror or extend versions of the widely used Hypertext Markup Language
	 (HTML), the language in which web pages are written.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>XSL</term>
		<definition>eXtensible Stylesheet Language</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>XSP</term>
		<definition>XML Server Pages</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>X-Query</term>
		<definition>XQuery is a query and functional programming language that is designed to query 
	collections of XML data.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Apache</term>
		<definition>Apache software projects are distributed with an open source license such
	as Apache HTTP server and many others.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Complexity theory</term>
		<definition>A branch of the theory of computation in computer science that focuses on classifying 
	computational problems according to their inherent difficulty.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Awt/Swing</term>
		<definition>Platform-independent windowing, graphics, and user-interface widget toolkits.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Gtk+</term>
		<definition>(GIMP Toolkit) is a cross-platform widget toolkit for creating graphical user
	 interfaces. It is one of the most popular toolkits for the X Window System,
	  along with Qt.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Tcl/Tk</term>
		<definition>Tcl (originally from "Tool Command Language", but conventionally rendered as "Tcl" 
	rather than "TCL" is a scripting language. It is commonly used for rapid prototyping, 
	scripted applications, GUIs and testing.
The combination of Tcl and the Tk GUI toolkit is referred to as Tcl/Tk.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>SDL</term>
		<definition>Multimedia library written in C that presents a simple interface to various platforms'
	 graphics, sound, and input devices.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>OpenGL</term>
		<definition>(Open Graphics Library) A standard specification defining a cross-language,
	 cross-platform API for writing applications that produce 2D and 3D computer graphics.
	  The interface consists of over 250 different function calls which can be used to draw 
	  complex three-dimensional scenes from simple primitives.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>TCP / UDP - IP</term>
		<definition>Transport Control Protocol - Uniform Data Protocol - Internet Protocol</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>BGP - IV</term>
		<definition>Border Gateway Protocol</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>SSH</term>
		<definition>Secured Shell</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>NAT</term>
		<definition>Network Address Translation</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>IPC</term>
		<definition>Inter-process communication</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Flex / Bison</term>
		<definition>Flex (fast lexical analyzer generator) is a free software alternative to lex. 
	It is frequently used with the free Bison parser generator.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>CamL</term>
		<definition>Caml (originally an acronym for Categorical Abstract Machine Language) is a dialect 
	of the ML programming language family, developed at INRIA and formerly at ENS.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>PageRank</term>
		<definition>PageRank is a link analysis algorithm, used by the Google Internet search engine 
	that assigns a numerical weighting to each element of a hyperlinked set of documents, 
	such as the World Wide Web, with the purpose of "measuring" its relative importance 
	within the set.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>OS</term>
		<definition>Operating System</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Unix / Linux</term>
		<definition>Unix (officially trademarked as UNIX, sometimes also written as Unix with small caps) 
	is a computer operating system originally developed in 1969.<br/>
	Linux is a generic term referring to Unix-like computer operating systems based on 
	the Linux kernel.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>SH / Bash / Csh / Tcsh</term>
		<definition>A shell is a piece of software that provides an interface for users.
Typically, the term refers to an operating system shell which provides access to the 
services of a kernel.
<br/><br/>
<u>Wiki:</u> <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shell_%28computing%29#Shells_for_programming_languages"> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shell_computing#Shells_for_programming_languages</a></definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Perl</term>
		<definition>Perl is a high-level, general-purpose, interpreted, dynamic programming language.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>Python</term>
		<definition>A general-purpose high-level programming language.Its design philosophy 
	emphasizes code readability. Python claims to "combine remarkable power with very 
	clear syntax, and its standard library is large and comprehensive. 
	Its use of indentation for block delimiters is unusual among popular programming 
	languages.</definition>
	</item>
	<item>
		<term>TOEIC</term>
		<definition>Test Of English for International Communication</definition>
	</item>
</glossary>