
<referees>
<letters>
	<item>
		<person>
		Thomas Nguyen
		</person>
		<email>
		thomas@vn.ibm.com
		</email>
		<title>
		Project Manager, Web Development Competency Leader, IBM Vietnam
		</title>
		<letter>
		RecommendationLetter_GA_TN.pdf
		</letter>
	</item>
	<item>
		<person>
		Jean Caussanel
		</person>
		<email>
		jean.caussanel@univ-cezanne.fr
		</email>
		<title>
		Enseignant-Chercheur &amp; Ma&icirc;tre de Conf&eacute;rences, Universit&eacute; Aix-Marseille III
		</title>
		<letter>
		RecommendationLetter_GA_JC.pdf
		</letter>
	</item>
	</letters>
	<linkedin>
	<item>
		<person>
		Hoai Anh Phan Nguyen
		</person>
		<profile>
		http://www.linkedin.com/pub/anh-phan/23/19b/245
		</profile>
		<title>
		Technical Project Manager, IO Media
                      a travaill&eacute; avec Gregory &agrave; IO-Network
		</title>
		<text>
		"Gregory never feels satisfied with the current working process and technology of the company. He keeps seeking restlessly for improvements and his efforts usually remains in much more productive ways of working things out. 
As a project manager, Gregory is best at project planning and risk management. After his first analysis and documentation, his staffs really have a clear direction to go. Projects under his management, therefore, are always delivered in time and in budget. 
Being his colleage for more than 1 year, I also learn many good things from Gregory Anne, both in technical issues and management issues."
                     --29 Novembre 2010
		</text>
	</item>
	<item>
		<person>
		Mahmoud Fatene
		</person>
		<profile>
		http://www.linkedin.com/pub/mahmoud-fatene/16/4b/5a4
		</profile>
		<title>
                  &Eacute;tudiant, University Joseph Fourier (Grenoble I),
                  a &eacute;tudi&eacute; avec Gregory &agrave; Universit&eacute; Joseph-Fourier Grenoble I
		</title>
		<text>
		"I knew Gregory Anne as a student in university of Joseph Fourier, 
  during this period I came to notice his human qualities as well as his high 
  involvement in the projects in which we have worked together. He later on accomplished 
  very high achievements in his scolarity which for me was the logical rewards to all 
  his work. I, therefore, highly recommend Gregory Anne for both his personal and 
  professional aptitudes." --25 Novembre 2009
		</text>
	</item>
	</linkedin>
</referees>